Guide to the Martin Shubik Papers, 1938-2017 and undated RL.01181
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Personal, 1938-2012; undated; 1
  - Letter to an old friend from Paris, 2003 (Box 46)
  - Miscellaneous personal files, 1966; 1975; 2011 (Box 126)
  - Name cards and postal cards, 2009; undated (Box 126)
  - Newspaper article about Yale's School of Organization and Management, undated (Box 46)
  - Newspaper article, Criteria for a More Effective Presidency, by M. Shubik, 1990 (Box 46)
  - Newspaper article, Master Museum Maker,Barron's, 1987 (Box 46)
  - Newspaper article, Prisoner's Dilemma in Personal Computing, November, 1979 (Box 46)
  - Newspaper article, Why are they Wrecking the Yale Business School? And how Will it Look on my CV?, 1989 (Box 46)
  - Newspaper articles, Yale Business School, 1990 (Box 46)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1970-1973; 2001-2003; undated (Box 129)
    Includes clippings related to colleagues and commentary given by Shubik
  - Notes on visit to Stanford University, October 16-17, 1980 (Box 46)
  - Notes on Washington trip to RAND office, November 2-7, 1970 (Box 46)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1938-2007; 16 folders (Box 129)
    Includes personal items and correspondence
  - Personnel security document, 1958-1980 (Box 126)
  - Poem: ENVOI, 1956 (Box 46)
  - Price list of Burma handrolled cigars, 1968 (Box 46)
  - Reminiscence by Shubik on his career, 1990s (Box 46)
  - Shubik quoted in newspaper, 1973 (Box 46)
  - Shubik, Curriculum Vitae, 1993; 2002 (Box 51)
  - Shubik, Irene, and other Shubik family members, 1951-1973 (Box 125)
  - Shubik's laws of long-range planning, undated (Box 46)
  - University of Toronto, 1944; 1949 (Box 129)
    Includes examination material
  - Various newspaper articles written by Kass, Douglas A. in Barron's, 1980s-1990s (Box 46)
  - Who's Who in the 21st Century Questionnaire and Curriculum Vitae, M. Shubik, 2001 (Box 46)